Akın Caner PEKEL

I have been involved in many projects as Mobile and Full Stack Developer and continue to work and support on various projects. I am experienced in B2B, B2C, accounting programs integration, Vehicle tracking systems, Legal Gambiling sites and Crypto Currency exchange sites.

597/3 street Number 8 Bayrakli Izmir/Turkey (+90) 505 280 85 52 akin_caner_pekel@hotmail.com

EXPERIENCE

S4IN A.Ş., Izmir/Turkey - Team Leader/Full Stack Developer

ocak 2018 - Continue

Proje Isleri, Izmir/Turkey - Junior Developer

August 2016 - ocak 2018

Izmir University, Izmir/Turkey - Project intern

aralık 2015 - mayıs 2016

Deka Digital, Izmir/Turkey - Summer intern

July 2015 - August 2015

EDUCATION

Ahmet Yesevi University - Cyber security Master's Degree

2021 - continue

Izmir University of Economics, - *Computer Engineering Bachelor degree*

2016 - 2019

ABILITIES

Python

Django

Angular(1 to 10)

Linux Server

Git

Ionic(1 to 4)

JavaScript

JQuery

HTML5

SCSS-CSS-SASS

LANGUAGES

English

Turkish